Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP B: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 202 SEATTLE, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-47/1, 69-73)
  - SERIES II: GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE of Administrative Staff, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-10/51)
    - Amalgamated Lithographers National Labor Relations Board, Part 1, 1956 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Amalgamated Lithographers National Labor Relations Board, Part 2, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Amnesty, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Trial Committee Noel versus Stewart, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Leo Noel vs. Douglas Stewart, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Krenz-Law-Mach to Proof Appeal, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Barrington O. Gayle International Typographical Union Appeal, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Malcolm Pace Appeal, 1975 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Charges against William Hanson by Richard Glenn, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Ferraro vs. Schwarz Charges and Trials, 1972 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Larry Hill Civil Case, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - United Farm Workers of America, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council, 1955-1977 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Label Insignia, c.1960-1972 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Portland Allied Printing Trades, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Tacoma Printing Trades Council, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Olympia Printing Trades Council, 1974 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Seattle School District Union Printing, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - The Mar-Lo Company, 1963 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Seattle Card and Label, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Tacoma Card and Label, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Everett Card and Label, c.1956-1975 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - King County Labor Council, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Kitsap County Labor Council, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - Labor Legislation Correspondence, 1950-1977 (Box-folder 9/31)
    - Pierce County Central Labor Council, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Snohomish County Labor Council, 1956 (Box-folder 9/33)
    - Whatcom County Labor Council, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 9/34)
    - Washington State Labor Council, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 9/35)
    - Washington State Labor Council, 1963-1976 (Box-folder 9/36)
    - Labor News, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 9/37)
    - Landrum-Griffin Act Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 9/38)
    - Anti-Strike Breaker, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 9/39)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Art Schmidt, 1943-1950 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Secretary John Gregory, 1947-1953 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Secretary J.M. Litonius, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Rue, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - President G.F. Stephens, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Executive Council, 1934 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Correspondence-School Board, Louis Siegel, J F Singer, C B Taylor, W E Weatman, 1923-1935 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Re: C.G. Smith, 1929-1933 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Secretary Randolph, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Vice President Perry "Organizational Work", 1929-1930 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - To Executive Council re: "Retained Employers"- Callahan Interview, 1929 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Secretary Randolph, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Secretary Randolph M. F. Vena Arrears, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Secretary Randolph re. A O Humphrey, 1932-1934 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council, 1935-1954 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Auditor's Quarterly Reports, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Auditor's Quarterly Reports, 1926-1941 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer Correspondence, 1936-1956 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - News Publishing, 1934-1957 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Correspondence, General Rules, Photo Prints, 1931-1943 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Litonius, J M, 1931 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Co-op Hart Bank, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, misc., 1928-1935 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - President Howard re. Statistics for Pacific Coast Labor, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - President Howard re. Violations of Priority by Foreman Winans, 1936 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - President Howard to President Litonius re. 1935 arbitration, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - President Howard "Priority" Sub-Vacations, Etc., 1936 (Box-folder 10/27)
    - President Howard- H F Kelly Guild Post-Intelligencer controversy, 1936 (Box-folder 10/28)
    - Apprentice- 5 or 6 day week President Howard- President Baker, 1936 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - Port Commission (Harry Listman letter), 1935 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - Star Chapel, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Progress Reports- Apprentice International Typographical Union Bureau of Education, 1929-1939 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Escrow Account Unemployment 3% Assets, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 10/33)
    - Melnikow, H.P., 1936 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Gale, Norman S Contributions, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 10/35)
    - "Protest" 1% Tax State Unemployment Tax, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 10/36)
    - Pacific Coast Labor Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 10/37)
    - Northwest Service Corporation, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Brotherhood Bank Union Record Pledge, 1922-1928 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Special Assistance Post-Intelligencer Chapel- Executive Council, 1936 (Box-folder 10/40)
    - McHale Contributions, 1938 (Box-folder 10/41)
    - Committees- Misc., 1931 (Box-folder 10/42)
    - Star Chapel, 1939-1945 (Box-folder 10/43)
    - Times Correspondence, 1915-1919 (Box-folder 10/44)
    - 1945 Strike (Newspaper), 1946 (Box-folder 10/45)
    - Strike Benefits, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10/46)
    - International Typographical Union Strike Benefits Local Strike Benefits, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10/47)
    - Seattle Central Labor Council, 1936-1954 (Box-folder 10/48)
    - Donations Paid through 1950, 1939-1954 (Box-folder 10/49)
    - Donations Paid 1951-1956 (Part 1), 1953-1956 (Box-folder 10/50)
    - Donations Paid 1951-1956 (Part 2), 1951-1953 (Box-folder 10/51)
  - SERIES III: GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE with other locals, 1918-1981 (Box-folder 11/1-12/31)
    - International Typographical Union Local Unions A Misc, 1928-1976 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Aberdeen 573, 1928-1975 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Anchorage 823, 1947-1963 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1977 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Bay Area 21, 1943-1974 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Bay Area 21, 1933-1981 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Bellingham 355, 1939-1974 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Bremerton 699, 1928-1974 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Chicago 16, 1934-1977 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Colorado Springs 82, 1936-1966 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1934-1975 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Columbia no. 101 Washington D.C, 1936-1973 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1929-1973 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Dallas No. 173, 1929-1967 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Denver 49, 1929-1974 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Des Moines No. 118, 1954-1970 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Detroit No. 18, 1926-1974 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Everett 410, 1928-1953 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1938-1951 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Fairbanks Local 639, 1950-1964 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1934-1970 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1930-1977 (Box-folder 11/23)
    - I Miscellaneous, 1925-1968 (Box-folder 11/24)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1949-1968 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1938-1973 (Box-folder 11/26)
    - Kansas City 80, 1929-1960 (Box-folder 11/27)
    - Kennewick-Pasco 831, 1950-1974 (Box-folder 11/28)
    - Ketchikan 822, 1943-1960 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1929-1968 (Box-folder 11/30)
    - Lewiston-Clarkston Typo Union 634, 1934-1963 (Box-folder 11/31)
    - Long Beach, Cal 650, 1923-1968 (Box-folder 11/32)
    - Longview-Kelso Typo No. 886 Part 1 of 2, 1931-1974 (Box-folder 11/33)
    - Longview-Kelso Typo No. 886 Part 2 of 2, 1931-1974 (Box-folder 11/34)
    - Los Angeles 174, 1924-1973 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1928-1975 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Portland (Multnomah) 58, 1923-1965 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1925-1976 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - New York 6, 1922-1976 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1929-1977 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Olympia 142, 1922-1975 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1928-1976 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Providence 33, 1937-1950 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Q Miscellaneous, 1936 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - R Miscellaneous, 1937-1977 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Sacramento 46, 1922-1977 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - San Diego 221, 1925-1973 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - St. Paul 30, 1918-1975 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Salem (Capital) 210, 1927-1963 (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Salt Lake City - 115, 1926-1968 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - San Antonio - 172, 1926-1973 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Seattle Mailers 32, 1960 (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Spokane Falls 193, 1924-1974 (Box-folder 12/19)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1933-1973 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1944-1972 (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Tacoma 170, 1922-1974 (Box-folder 12/22)
    - U Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 12/23)
    - V Miscellaneous, 1930-1970 (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Vancouver B.C. 226, 1921-1977 (Box-folder 12/25)
    - Vancouver Washington 947, 1936-1975 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Victoria B.C. 201, 1941-1972 (Box-folder 12/27)
    - W Miscellaneous, 1936-1964 (Box-folder 12/28)
    - Walla Walla 388, 1935-1959 (Box-folder 12/29)
    - Wenatchee 680, 1934-1970 (Box-folder 12/30)
    - Yakima 614, 1928-1974 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - SERIES IV: ELECTION RESULTS - Union officers, 1934-1973 (Box-folder 13/1-14/15)
    - International Typographical Union Referendum-1973 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - 1972 Referendum- International Typographical Union (Box-folder 13/2)
    - International Typographical Union Referendum-1970-1971 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Comparative Scales, c.1958-1962 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - 1973 Elections (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Elections -1972 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Elections -1971 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Elections - 1970 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - 1966 Nominations and Elections (Box-folder 13/9)
    - 1965 Election Officers and Delegates (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Elections - 1964 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Elections - 1963 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Elections - 1962 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Elections - 1961 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - 1960 Elections (Box-folder 13/15)
    - 1959 Elections (Box-folder 13/16)
    - 1958 Elections (Box-folder 13/17)
    - 1957 Elections (Box-folder 13/18)
    - 1956 Elections (Box-folder 13/19)
    - 1955 Elections (Box-folder 13/20)
    - 1954 Elections (Box-folder 13/21)
    - 1953 Elections (Box-folder 13/22)
    - 1952 Elections (Box-folder 13/23)
    - 1951 Elections (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Referendum 1950, c.1950-1957 (Box-folder 13/25)
    - 1950 Elections (Box-folder 13/26)
    - 1949 Elections (Box-folder 13/27)
    - 1948 Elections (Box-folder 13/28)
    - 1947 Elections (Box-folder 13/29)
    - 1946 Election (Box-folder 14/1)
    - 1945 Election (Box-folder 14/2)
    - 1944 Election (Box-folder 14/3)
    - 1943 Election (Box-folder 14/4)
    - 1942 Election (Box-folder 14/5)
    - 1941 Election (Box-folder 14/6)
    - 1940 Election (Box-folder 14/7)
    - 1939 Election (Box-folder 14/8)
    - 1938 Election (Box-folder 14/9)
    - 1937 Election (Box-folder 14/10)
    - 1936 Election (Box-folder 14/11)
    - 1935 Election (Box-folder 14/12)
    - 1934 Election (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Taft-Hartley, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - International Typographical Union, 1965 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - SERIES V: GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE - With Presses, 1938-1973 (Box-folder 14/16-14/45)
    - Local 202-Legal Correspondence, Part 1, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Local 202-Legal Correspondence, Part 2, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Local 202-Legal Correspondence, Part 3, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Local 202-Legal Correspondence, Part 4, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Local Bylaws Amended to February 23, 1967. Changes Adopted Since February 24, 1968 Binder, Part 1, c.1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Local Bylaws Amended to February 23, 1967. Changes Adopted Since February 24, 1968 Binder, Part 1, c.1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Bellingham Herald, 1976 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Kane and Harcus, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Lowman and Hadford, 1932-1971 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Metropolitan - Western, 1930-1969 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - News Publishing 1958, Part 1, 1958-1976 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - News Publishing 1958, Part 2, 1958-1976 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - News Publishing 1958, Part 3, 1958-1976 (Box-folder 14/28)
    - News Publishing 1958, Part 4, 1958-1976 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - North Central Outlook, 1948-1972 (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Northwest Envelope, 1939-1964 (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Snohomish Tribune, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Tillikum Press, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 14/33)
    - United Graphics, 1938-1971 (Box-folder 14/34)
    - White Center, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 14/35)
    - News Stories and Edits Re:Joint Strike, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 14/36)
    - Material Helper in Preparing Ads, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 14/37)
    - Correspondence with Firms Dealing Directly with Kenny Dale, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/38)
    - Letters to Advertisers Re: Joint Strikes, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 14/39)
    - Ads and Handbills Approved by Jackson Notices Sent to Members, Part 1, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 14/40)
    - Ads and Handbills Approved by Jackson Notices Sent to Members, Part 1, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 14/41)
    - Letters-Candidates Joint Strike Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 14/42)
    - Letters-Labor Organizations Joint Strike Committee, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 14/43)
    - Tacoma-Lakewood, 1964 (Box-folder 14/44)
    - Valley Publishing Company, 1962 (Box-folder 14/45)
  - SERIES VI: MINUTES - GENERAL MEETINGS, 1882-1974 (Box-folder 15/1-18/25)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union Local 202 Minutes, November 1882-June 1888, 1882-1888 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1888-February 1892, 1888-1892 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, March 1892-January 1893, 1892-1893 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1893-July 1893 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, August 1893-May 1894, 1893-1894 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, June 1894-June 1896, 1894-1896 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1896- January 1899, 1896-1899 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1899-January 1900, 1899-1900 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1900-December 1901, 1900-1901 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1902-December 1903 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1904-December 1905 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1906-June 1907, 1906-1907 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1908 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-July 1909 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, August-December 1909 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1910 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1910 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-March 1911 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, April-December 1911 (Box-folder 15/19)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1912 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1912 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1913 (Box-folder 15/22)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1913 (Box-folder 15/23)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1914 (Box-folder 15/24)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1914 (Box-folder 15/25)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1915 (Box-folder 15/26)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes July-December 1915 (Box-folder 15/27)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1916 - June 1916 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1916 - January 1917 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1917 - June 1917 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1917 - December 1917 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1918 - June 1918 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1918 - December 1918 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1919 - June 1919 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1919 - December 1919 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1920 - June 1920 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1920 - December 1920 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1921 - June 1921 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1921 - December 1921 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1922 - June 1922 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1922 - December 1922 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1923 - June 1923 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1923 - December 1923 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1924 - April 1924 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1924 - August 1924 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, September 1924 - December 1924 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1925 - June 1925 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1925 - December 1925 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1926 - June 1926 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1926 - December 1926 (Box-folder 16/23)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1927 - June 1927 (Box-folder 16/24)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1927 - December 1927 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1928 - June 1928 (Box-folder 16/26)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1928 - December 1928 (Box-folder 16/27)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1929 - June 1929 (Box-folder 16/28)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1929 - December 1929 (Box-folder 16/29)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1930 - June 1930 (Box-folder 16/30)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1930 - December 1930 (Box-folder 16/31)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1931 - June 1931 (Box-folder 16/32)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1931 - December 1931 (Box-folder 16/33)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1932 - April 1932 (Box-folder 16/34)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1932 - August 1932 (Box-folder 16/35)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, September 1932 - December 1932 (Box-folder 16/36)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1933 - March 1933 (Box-folder 16/37)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, April 1933 (Box-folder 16/38)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1933 - June 1933 (Box-folder 16/39)